Aji Tri Hardono

Ajitrih7@gmail | https://www.linkedin.com/in/aji-tri-hardono-a90a84212/ | 085727234413

Profile

D4 Demographic and Civil Registration graduate with internship experience at the Population and Civil Registration Service in 3 regions (Klaten, Wonogiri, Purwodadi), understanding the basics of programming, experience in the digital world as moderator/admin for crypto groups (Safemoon, Real Metaverse, Moon Natuon games)

EXPERIENCES

Realy Metaverse Admin/Moderator

(January 2022 - April 2022)

Managing Realy Metaverse Indonesia cryptocurrency group

Moon Nation Game

(September 2021 - December 2021)

Managing Moon nation game cryptocurrency group

Safemoon.ltd

Admin/Moderator

Admin/Moderator (April 2021 - September 2021)

Managing Safemoon Indonesia cryptocurrency group

Adnan & Co

Paralegal (September 2020 - September 2020)

Assisting input customer data in the case of the savings and loans

EDUCATION

Universitas Sebelas Maret

(September 2017 - July 2021)

GPA: 3.74 / 4.00

Bachelors D4 Demografi dan Pencatatan Sipil

2nd Runner Up Lomba Karya Tulis Tingkat Nasional di IPDN 2019

3rd place The best presentation Lomba Karya Tulis Tingkat Nasional di IPDN

2019

2nd Runner Up Lomba Karya Tulis Tingkat Nasional di Universitas Halu Oleo 2020

ORGANIZATIONS

Staff Advocations | BEM FH UNS

(January 2018 - January 2019)

- Serves as an intermediary between students and the dean so that the right information can be created and maximizes information from the dean to students.
- To catch aspiration from students to dean to make considerations in making decisions.

General Chairman | Community of Klaten UNS

(June 2018 - July 2019)

 in charge of coordinating and supervising the projects of the Klaten Surakarta Student Families, among others, the fostered hamlets, Tryout PTNs in Klaten Regency, Klaten Tourism Promotions, Photo and Video Contests, etc.

LANGUANGES

- Indonesian (Expert)
- English (Good)

SKILLS

Communication | Leadership | Analytical Thinking | Microsoft Office (Expert) | Bahasa pemrograman **HTML/CSS** (Middle),Bahasa Pemrograman **C++** (Beginner), English (Good), Indonesian language (Expert